Guide to the Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records, ca. 1960-1989
Visual Services / Cornell Publications Photography records,
- Series I. Assignments
  - September 1988
    - Baker Inst. Dedication, 880911 (Box 19)
    - Computer Services in WSH, 880912 (Box 19)
    - Aerials, 880913 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum, 880914 (Box 19)
    - Mare and Foal for Christmas Card, 880915 (Box 19)
    - Copy Work, 880916 (Box 19)
    - [illegible] Sage Hall, 880917 (Box 19)
  - October 1988
    - Engineering - Dick White, 881001 (Box 19)
    - Engineering - David Schimmel, 881002 (Box 19)
    - Arts Council, 881003 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 881004 (Box 19)
    - Presidential Councillors, 881005 (Box 19)
    - Bartels Lecture Series / Statler tour & Tailgating, 881006 (Box 19)
    - Engineering - cars on Quad, 881007 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum- visiting speaker, 881008 (Box 19)
    - Law School Foot Race, 881009 (Box 19)
    - Humphreys Service Building & Computers, 881010 (Box 19)
    - Trustees at Law School, 881011 (Box 19)
    - Hotel School, 881012 (Box 19)
    - Bartels Lecture series w Ambass. Laingen, 881013 (Box 19)
    - Federalist Symposium, 881014 (Box 19)
    - Copy Neg, 881015 (Box 19)
    - Arts & Science Faculty, 881016 (Box 19)
    - Theory Center Groundbreaking, 881017 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 881018 (Box 19)
    - ILR, C.S. (120 B & W, 881019 (Box 19)
  - November 1988
    - Big Red Bears, 881101 (Box 19)
    - Untitled, 881102 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum, Prof. Strum, 881103 (Box 19)
    - PAC at night, 881104 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 881105 (Box 19)
    - Law Forum, Prof. Kennedy, 881106 (Box 19)
    - Dan Schorr, Nordlander Lecture Series, 881107 (Box 19)
    - Hopcroft / Campbell / Baer / Call / Norton, 881108 (Box 19)
    - Big Red Bears, 881109 (Box 19)
    - Hotel Tailgating, 881110 (Box 19)
    - Untitled, 881111 (Box 19)
    - PAC / Big Red Band, 881112 (Box 19)
  - December 1988
    - Professor Strauss, 881201 (Box 19)
    - Ann Weibel, 881202 (Box 19)
    - Performing Arts Center Dance Studio Interior, 881203 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Professors and Grad Areas, 881204 (Box 19)
    - Students at Citizen's Bank, 881205 (Box 19)
    - Engineering, 881206 (Box 19)
    - A. D. White Library, 881207 (Box 19)
    - Students Studying, 881208 (Box 19)
    - Sibley Interior, 881209 (Box 19)
    - Statler Christmas Party at Ramada Inn, 881210 (Box 19)
  - January 1989
    - Natl. Nanofabrication Facility Director, Harold Craighead, 890101 (Box 19)
    - Baker Lab Faculty, 890102 (Box 19)
    - A.D. White Library, 890103 (Box 19)
    - Johnson Museum Interiors, 890104 (Box 19)
    - Sibley Gallery and Interiors, 890105 (Box 19)
    - Cascadilla and PAC Exteriors, 890106 (Box 19)
  - February 1989
    - Arts and Sciences, 890201 (Box 19)
    - Hotel School, 890202 (Box 19)
    - Snow Scenes, 890203 (Box 19)
    - Near East Studies, 890204 (Box 19)
    - Law School, 890205 (Box 19)
    - Wilson Synchrotron, 890206 (Box 19)
    - Temple of Zeus, 890207 (Box 19)
    - Dean Streett (Engineering) with Students, 890208 (Box 19)
    - PAC Interior, 890209 (Box 19)
    - Dr. Catherine Haupt with Horse and Husband, 890210 (Box 19)
    - Law School Lecturer- David Hsin-Shih Chang, 890211 (Box 19)
  - March 1989
    - Performing Arts Center (PAC) Interiors, 890301 (Box 19)
    - Foundry, 890302 (Box 19)
    - Wind Ensemble - Bailey Hall, 890303 (Box 19)
    - Green Dragon, 890304 (Box 19)
    - Copy Negs., 890305 (Box 19)
    - Dedication- (Schwartz, 890306 (Box 19)
    - Snow Scenes, 890307 (Box 19)
    - Hotel Placement Office, 890308 (Box 19)
    - Orchestra - Bailey Hall, 890309 (Box 19)
    - HEPS - track, 890310 (Box 19)
    - Provost Barker and Mike Withiam, 890311 (Box 19)
    - Law School Lecturer, 890312 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Lecturer, 890313 (Box 19)
    - Sculpture Class and Mud Sliding, 890314 (Box 19)
    - Cornell Information Technologies, 890315 (Box 19)
    - Kaufman Auditorium Lecturer, 890316 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Copy Negs., 890317 (Box 19)
  - April 1989
    - IBM Press conference at Statler, 890401 (Box 19)
    - Law School - Csaba Varga - Visiting Lecturer, 890403 (Box 19)
    - Law School celebration, 890404 (Box 19)
    - Black Alumni, 890405 (Box 19)
    - Biological Sciences, 890406 (Box 19)
    - HEC, 890407 (Box 19)
    - Rob Osborne - Recycling, 890408 (Box 19)
    - Joan Williams - Law School, 890409 (Box 19)
    - Fred Hart Engineering School, 890410 (Box 19)
    - Ampitheater, 890411 (Box 19)
    - Textile Design, 890412 (Box 19)
    - Spike Lee, 890413 (Box 19)
    - Engineering, 890414 (Box 19)
    - Law School, 890415 (Box 19)
    - Engineering cBash on Quad, 890416 (Box 19)
    - National Nanofabrication Facility (NNF, 890417 (Box 19)
    - Hotel School Fashion Show, 890418A (Box 19)
    - Egg Drop, 890418B (Box 19)
  - May 1989
    - Cornell recycles, 890501 (Box 19)
    - Arts & Sciences, 890502 (Box 19)
    - Law Lecture, 890503 (Box 19)
    - Biotechnology, 890504 (Box 19)
    - Law School, 890505 (Box 19)
    - Music Faculty, 890506 (Box 19)
    - Beebe Lake Daffodills, 890507 (Box 19)
    - Biotech Dedication, 890508 (Box 19)
    - Defrees Hydrolic Lab Ceremony, 890509 (Box 19)
    - United Newspapers Group (JGSM, 890510 (Box 19)
    - Former Pres. Of Gambia, 890511 (Box 19)
    - George Peter Dedication (Hotel, 890512 (Box 19)
    - Presidential Scholars, 890513 (Box 19)
    - Law School Profs, 890514 (Box 19)
    - Landmark Plaque, 890515 (Box 19)
    - Theory Center VIP's, 890516 (Box 19)
    - Commencement, 890517 (Box 19)
  - June 1989
    - Engineering - NNF, 890601 (Box 19)
    - Center for Theatre Arts, 890602 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 890603 (Box 19)
    - Untitled, 890604 (Box 19)
    - Jerry Feist & Steve Verona, 890605 (Box 19)
    - Law School, 890606 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 890607 (Box 19)
    - NILFISK -NNF, 890608 (Box 19)
    - Service Awards Banquet, 890609 (Box 19)
    - Abba Eban, 890610 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Professors, 890611 (Box 19)
    - Human Ecology, 890612 (Box 19)
    - Law School Reunion, 890613 (Box 19)
    - Hotel School - Coors visit, 890614 (Box 19)
    - Hotel CPD program (see July also, 890615 (Box 19)
    - Reunion Univ. Address, 890616 (Box 19)
    - Biotech, 890617 (Box 19)
    - Mathematical Scientific Institute, 890618 (Box 19)
    - Sibley interior, 890619 (Box 19)
    - CCC, 890620 (Box 19)
    - El. Engineering Group, 890621 (Box 19)
    - Hotel CPD Scholarship dinner, 890622 (Box 19)
  - July 1989
    - CPD - Hotel, 890701 (Box 19)
    - Engineering bridge building, 890702 (Box 19)
    - Engineering Conference, 890703 (Box 19)
    - NNF - Installation of nitrogen tank, 890704 (Box 19)
    - Students in MVR focus group, 890705 (Box 19)
    - C.S., 890706 (Box 19)
    - NNF week long seminar, 890707 (Box 19)
    - Engineering - grad & undergrad in Bard Hall, 890708 (Box 19)
    - Hotel - wedding reception set-up, 890709 (Box 19)
- Series II. Slides
  - Slides in sleeves, 1970's
    Boxes 1-3, Sol Goldberg
    - Category #1 Alumni University
      - Peter Kahn (Box 1)
      - A.D. White House (Box 1)
      - Kaufman Auditorium (Box 1)
      - O'Brien/Seznec/McCue/Austin (Box 1)
      - Art Neal/Mike Covert (Box 1)
      - Finn Family (Box 1)
      - Buses/Kids/Water/Spagetti (Box 1)
      - Duke Ellington (Box 1)
      - Classrooms (Box 1)
      - Game Farm (Box 1)
      - Orno Lab (Box 1)
      - Bee Lab/Kids (Box 1)
      - Dick Lewis/Plantations (Box 1)
      - Pheasants (Box 1)
      - Guitarist (Box 1)
      - Coffee Hour (Box 1)
      - Zeus/CAU (Box 1)
      - Chines Professors (Box 1)
      - Pinball Machines (Box 1)
      - Moon Dust (Box 1)
      - Crick Pollution (Box 1)
      - Mary Donlon Lounges (Box 1)
      - Space Science Labs (Box 1)
      - Stewart Park (Box 1)
      - Anthony Caputi (Box 1)
      - Video Camera (Box 1)
      - Jack Warner/Joe Leeming/Helen Hamilton (Box 1)
      - North Campus (Box 1)
      - Alumni Families (Box 1)
      - Park Rides/Kids (Box 1)
      - 1970 CAU Professors (Box 1)
      - Kids/Nap/Hiking (Box 1)
      - Martie Young (Box 1)
    - Category #2 Arecibo/SYNCHROTRON
      - FrankDrake (Box 1)
      - Credits (Box 1)
      - Dish (Box 1)
      - Chicken Wire (Box 1)
      - Super Stucture (Box 1)
      - Message (Box 1)
      - Aerial (Box 1)
      - 3 Flags (Box 1)
      - Workers in Dish (Box 1)
      - Interiors (Box 1)
      - Flowers (Box 1)
      - Corson (Box 1)
      - Pulsar (Box 1)
      - Upgrading Dedication (Box 1)
      - Sunset (Box 1)
      - Night Views (Box 1)
      - Construction Area (Box 1)
      - Hills (Box 1)
      - Syncrotron/Oval/Matyas (Box 1)
    - Category #3 B & PA
      - Executive Development Program/Classrooms (Box 1)
      - Computers (Box 1)
      - Organizational Charts (Box 1)
      - Library (Box 1)
      - Exteriors (Box 1)
      - Dean Thomas (Box 1)
      - Balch Auditorium (Box 1)
      - Classrooms (Box 1)
      - Students (Box 1)
      - Chess (Box 1)
      - Professors (Box 1)
      - Lounge (Box 1)
      - Sculpture (Box 1)
      - Malott Hall (Box 1)
      - T.C. Hospital Emergency Room (Box 1)
      - Walter Carpenter (Box 1)
      - Stairwells (Box 1)
      - Nurses (Box 1)
      - Ned Flash (Box 1)
      - T.C. Court House (Box 1)
      - McAdams/Earl Brooks (Box 1)
      - Alumni/Wellelman (Box 1)
      - Charles McCord (Box 1)
      - Collyer Room (Box 1)
      - Directory (Box 1)
      - Prof. Hass/Gilmore/Weich/Battistella/Broyos Ridenour/Bierman/Carter (Box 1)
      - Alumni/Meaken/Simpson/Winnert (Box 1)
      - Bennett/1st National (Box 1)
      - Exedutive Office/Washington (Box 1)
      - U.S. Securities & Exchange Committee-Washington (Box 1)
      - Visiting Executives/Auditorium/Small rooms (Box 1)
      - Dean Davidson (Box 1)
      - Hopkins/Admissions (Box 1)
    - Category #4 People
      - Corson (Box 1)
      - Kiplinger (Box 1)
      - Charts & Grafts (Box 1)
      - Commencement (Box 1)
      - Peter Kellogg/Ornitholigist (Box 1)
      - Pew Quad Dedication/Engineering (Box 1)
    - Category #5 Athletics
      - Marinaro/Still/Action (Box 1)
      - Beig Red Band/Big Red Bear (Box 1)
      - Crowds (Box 1)
      - Schoellkopf Field (Box 1)
      - Joe Holland (Box 1)
      - C.U. vs Yale (Box 1)
      - Football (Box 1)
      - 150 lb Football (Box 1)
      - Jack Musick/Coach (Box 1)
      - Mark Allen (Box 1)
      - Flag (Box 1)
      - Cheerleaders (Box 1)
      - George Seifert/Coach (Box 1)
      - Giants/Steelers-Pro Game (Box 1)
      - Gary Wood/Gogelach (Box 1)
      - Carmen Piccone (Box 1)
      - Coaching Staff '67 (Box 1)
      - Hoy Field-Practice (Box 1)
      - Training Room (Box 1)
      - Helmets (Box 1)
      - Lacrosse (Box 1)
      - Hockey (Box 1)
      - Lynah Rink (Box 1)
      - Crew/Inlet (Box 1)
      - Jong Collyer & Oarsmen (Box 1)
      - Cottage on Lake (Box 1)
      - IRA Regatta/Syracuse (Box 1)
      - Sailing/Cayuga Lake (Box 1)
      - B.M.A. (Box 1)
      - Ken Dryden/Hockey (Box 2)
      - Harkness/Hockey (Box 2)
      - Tufford (Box 2)
      - NCAA Trophy (Box 2)
      - Crowds/Hockey/Action '76 (Box 2)
      - Lacrosse/Action '77/Hopkins/Helmets/TV/Lower Alumni (Box 2)
      - Richie Moran/Coach (Box 2)
      - Basketball '67 (Box 2)
      - Bob Kane on TV (Box 2)
      - Basketball (Box 2)
      - Dave Dupe/Shot Put (Box 2)
      - Heptagonals (Box 2)
      - Coach Harrison Sanford/Crew (Box 2)
      - Mrs. Sanford (Box 2)
      - Penn Coach/'69 (Box 2)
    - Category #7 Isle of Shoals
      - Scenics (Box 2)
      - Seagulls (Box 2)
      - Flora (Box 2)
      - Classes (Box 2)
      - Labs (Box 2)
      - Houses (Box 2)
      - Codking (Box 2)
      - Fog (Box 2)
      - Water (Box 2)
      - Ocean (Box 2)
      - Butterfly (Box 2)
      - Sunset (Box 2)
      - Groups (Box 2)
      - Professors (Box 2)
      - Spider Web (Box 2)
      - Lobster (Box 2)
      - Custard Pies (Box 2)
      - Microscropes (Box 2)
      - Island (Box 2)
      - Sign (Box 2)
    - Category #8 Commencement
      - Arts Quad (Box 2)
      - Corson/Barton/Degree Recipients (Box 2)
      - Mace (Box 2)
      - Cameras (Box 2)
      - Families (Box 2)
      - Processions (Box 2)
      - Schoelkopf Field (Box 2)
      - Pollack/Cranch (Box 2)
      - Caps & Gowns (Box 2)
      - ROTC (Box 2)
      - Student Trustees (Box 2)
      - Protest Signs (Box 2)
      - Blanchard Rideout (Box 2)
      - Dean Davidson/Cap & Gown (Box 2)
      - Orientals (Box 2)
      - Cowboy Hat (Box 2)
      - George Healey w/Mace (Box 2)
      - Odd Caps & Gowns (Box 2)
      - Hawaiian (Box 2)
      - Grads/Andy & Ezra/Airplanes/Engineers (Box 2)
      - Cap & Gown Covered Kiosk (Box 2)
      - Chefs Caps (Box 2)
      - Trustees (Box 2)
      - Frisbees/Balloons (Box 2)
      - Hugging & Kissing (Box 2)
      - Minorities/Foreign Students (Box 2)
      - Podium/VIPS (Box 2)
      - Crowds (Box 2)
      - Before/During/After (Box 2)
      - ETC. (Box 2)
    - Category #9 Reunion Alumni
      - Corson with Alumni (Box 2)
      - Booths in Barton (Box 2)
      - Menu '74 (Box 2)
      - Walking on Campus (Box 2)
      - Kids/Activities (Box 2)
      - Statler Auditorium/Panel (Box 2)
      - Brud Holland (Box 2)
      - ILR/Booth/Barton (Box 2)
      - Human Development & Family/Booth/Barton (Box 2)
      - Mr. & Mrs. Allen Treman (Box 2)
      - C.U. Sun Booth (Box 2)
      - Million Dollar Class (Box 2)
      - Savage Club Show (Box 2)
      - Guitarist/Juggler (Box 2)
      - Allen Treman Act (Box 2)
      - Career Center (Box 2)
      - Chromasomes in Chicks (Box 2)
      - Bio Science (Box 2)
      - Vet School (Box 2)
      - Engineering (Box 2)
      - China-Japan Program (Box 2)
      - Dean of Students Offices (Box 2)
      - Arecibo (Box 2)
      - Cooperative Extension (Box 2)
      - Oarsmen (Box 2)
      - Food Line Up (Box 2)
      - Women's Breakfast (Box 2)
      - 1947 Headquarters (Box 2)
      - Gus Requardt & Friends (Box 2)
      - 1943 Sign (Box 2)
      - Plantations (Box 2)
      - Class of '18 (Box 2)
      - Welcome Signs (Box 2)
    - Category #10 Film Strips/Slide Shows
      - Admissions Film Strip (Box 2)
      - "Aspects" (Box 2)
      - Morris Bishop (Box 2)
      - Credits (Box 2)
      - Berkley Show (Box 2)
      - 1955 B/W Archive Reunion (Box 2)
      - Collegetown (Box 2)
      - Seth Goldschlager (Box 2)
      - CUAA Show (Box 2)
      - Credits (Box 2)
      - Cranch Report/Panel (Box 2)
      - Archives Slides (Box 2)
      - "Cornell Idea" (Box 2)
      - Cornell Scrapbook Ephemera (Box 2)
      - Tower Club Gift Chart (Box 2)
      - Hayden Planetarium Show (Box 2)
      - "Earthly" Show (Box 2)
    - Category #11 Plantations
      - Fall-in (Box 2)
      - People/Kids/Foreign Students/Golden Temple Gardener (Box 2)
      - 1973 (Box 2)
      - Balloons (Box 2)
      - Dave Dunlop (Box 2)
      - Bus/Quilt (Box 2)
      - Hypar (Box 2)
      - Horse Drawn Wagon (Box 2)
      - Tractor/Pumpkins (Box 2)
      - Troubadours (Box 2)
      - Crowds (Box 2)
    - Category #13 Dedications
      - New York Convocation (Box 3)
      - Willard Straight/Corson/Receiving Line (Box 3)
      - Bailey Hall Orientation (Box 3)
      - Convocation/Rochester (Box 3)
      - Presidential Councillors (Box 3)
      - Chemical Research Building (Box 3)
      - Spencer Olin/Family (Box 3)
      - Al Saperston (Box 3)
      - Herbert F. Johnson Museum Opening (Box 3)
      - Hib Johnson (Box 3)
      - Fireworks/4th of July at Schoellkopf Events (Box 3)
      - International Drum Corps Competition/Schoellkopf (Box 3)
      - Flags/Trumpets/Marching/Etc. (Box 3)
    - Category #14 Students/Activities/Registration
      - Student Closeups (Box 3)
      - Risley Fair (Box 3)
      - Outdoor Scenes (Box 3)
      - Arts Quad/Exhibits (Box 3)
      - Song of the Vowels (Box 3)
      - Libe Slope (Box 3)
      - Fiji (Box 3)
      - Class Rings (Box 3)
      - Collegetown (Box 3)
      - Trees (Box 3)
      - Kids (Box 3)
      - Dining Room/Frat. (Box 3)
      - Blood Donors (Box 3)
      - Green Dragon (Box 3)
      - Exams (Box 3)
      - Drinking (Box 3)
      - Glee Club Tour/Asia (Box 3)
      - Zeus (Box 3)
      - Christmas Concert (Box 3)
      - Reistration (Box 3)
      - Arrival (Box 3)
      - Activities (Box 3)
      - Cornell Senate (Box 3)
      - Spring/Summer/Fall (Box 3)
      - Minorities (Box 3)
      - Fun in the Sun (Box 3)
      - Beg Red Band (Box 3)
      - Msical Groups (Box 3)
      - Springfest (Box 3)
      - Octoberfest (Box 3)
      - Bicycles (Box 3)
      - Swings (Box 3)
      - Outdoor Classes (Box 3)
      - University Senate Wreath (Box 3)
    - Category #15 Campus Scenes/Outdoors
      - Campus Map Sign near Rand Hall (Box 3)
      - Arts Quad (Every which way?) (Box 3)
      - Libe Tower/Slope (Box 3)
      - Willard Straight/Stump (Box 3)
      - Sage Chapel (Box 3)
      - Trees/Elms (Box 3)
      - Willard Straight Hall (Box 3)
      - Rockefeller Hall (Box 3)
      - Morril/Construction (Box 3)
      - Suspension Bridge (Box 3)
      - Sculpture/Arts Quad (Box 3)
      - Engineering/Quad (Box 3)
      - Professor Eastman (Box 3)
      - Myron Taylor Hall (Box 3)
      - War Memorial (Box 3)
      - Dorm Rooms (Box 3)
      - Garbage (Box 3)
      - Balch Auditorium (Box 3)
      - 68 Dress (Box 3)
      - Snow/Libe Slope (Box 3)
      - Vet School (Box 3)
      - Ag Quad/Trees (Box 3)
      - Gorges (Box 3)
      - Sapsucker Woods (Box 3)
      - Teagle Hall/Rand Hall (Box 3)
      - Kapa/Slides (Box 3)
      - Snow Scenes (Box 3)
      - Hotel Ezra Cornell (Box 3)
      - Hotel School (Box 3)
      - Art Museum (Box 3)
      - Collegetown (Box 3)
      - Fiji (Box 3)
      - Olin Libe/Uris Libe (Box 3)
      - Spring/Summer (Box 3)
      - Outdoor Classes (Box 3)
      - ROTC (Box 3)
    - Category #16 Classrooms/Libraries/New York
      - Indor Classes (Box 3)
      - LaFeber (Box 3)
      - Eastman (Box 3)
      - A.D. White Museum/Interiors (Box 3)
      - Statler/Lectures (Box 3)
      - Photo Darkroom (Box 3)
      - Cornell Senate (Box 3)
      - Chemistry Lab (Box 3)
      - Library Interiors (Box 3)
      - Medical College/New York City (Box 3)
      - Vet School Operations (Box 3)
      - Architecture Class (Box 3)
      - Hotel School (Box 3)
      - Computers/Hotel School (Box 3)
    - Category #17 Minorities
      - "Black is Beautiful" Show (Box 3)
      - Interview/WCNY (Box 3)
      - Black Musicians (Box 3)
      - Black Actors (Box 3)
      - Africana Center (Box 3)
      - Dog Show/Arts Quad (Box 3)
    - Category #18 1977-1978
      - Dale Corson 18 slides (Box 3)
      - Austin Kiplinger 12 slides (Box 3)
      - Corson and Kiplinger 7 slides (Box 3)
      - Frank Rhodes Inauguration 181 slides (Box 3)
      - Christmas tree, presidents office 10 slides (Box 3)
      - Commencement, 1977 245 slides (Box 3)
  - Slides sets in sleeves w/cassettes (Box 10)
    - Arecibo 7/75 (Box 10)
    - CU Athletics (Box 10)
    - Engineering Quad Aerials (Box 10)
    - Rhodes/Kiplinger Dialogues (Box 10)
    - Isle of Shoals (Box 10)
    - The Minority Experience at Cornell (Box 10)
    - "It Takes More Than Books" Library Show (Box 10)
    - Cornell Chronicle: A Pictorial Review #1 (Box 10)
    - Cornell Chronicle: A Pictorial Review #2 (Box 10)
    - Cornell Chronicle: A Pictorial Review #3 (Box 10)
    - Cornell Chronicle: A Pictorial Review #4 (Box 10)
    - Facetime and Alumni Song (Box 10)
    - Facetime Music (Box 10)
    - Facetime/Alumni Song cassette (Box 10)
    - Extra Slides (Box 10)
    - Cornell Professors (Box 10)
    - Cornellians and Cornell (Box 10)
    - To Nobly Believe (Box 10)
    - Alumni University - Alumni Song (Box 10)
    - Slides and audio tapes for presentations (Box 10)
    - "Soundtracks" produced by Office of Public Information (Box 10)
    - "Cornell Alumni University" (Box 10)
    - "Dialogue" Corson interviewd by Austin Kiplinger (Box 10)
    - "There Are Few Earthly Things More Beautiful Than A University" (Box 10)
  - Slides: Miscellaneous
    - Slides - in boxes, sets, dupes (Box 4)
    - Slides - in large boxes, some loose, 1960s-19870s (Box 5)
    - Slides - in boxes, cassettes. Cornell Review (Box 6)
    - Slides in sleeves, by subject, 1970s-1980s (Box 7)
    - Slides - in plastic and cardboard boxes, by subject 1970's-80's (Box 8)
    - Slides in sleeves, by subject (Box 9)
    - Slides in sleeves, by subject (Box 11)
    - Slides in sleeves, by subject (Box 12)
    - Slides in sleeves, by subject (Box 13)